{
    "questions":
        [
            {
                "question": "Final methods can be overloaded.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "An anonymous class cannot have an explicitly declared constructor.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "Java final class can be a superclass.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "false"
            },
            {
                "question": "Methods that are declared as final or static cannot be overridden.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "Super class reference variables can always point to subclass objects.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which data types the number 132 can fit?",
                "choices": ["int", "short", "long", "byte"],
                "type": "select",
                "correctAnswer": ["int", "short", "long"]
            },
            {
                "question": "The switch statement works with which of the following?",
                "choices": ["int", "String", "float", "long"],
                "type": "select",
                "correctAnswer": ["int", "String"]
            },
            {
                "question": "There can be only one public top-level class per .java file.",
                "choices": ["true", "false"],
                "type": "radio",
                "correctAnswer": "true"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "int[] arr = {0,0,0,0,0};<br>int x = 0;int y = 2;<br>for (int i = 0; i < 10; i +=2) {arr[x] = y + i;x++;}<br>System.out.print(arr[3]);",
                "type": "input",
                "correctAnswer": "8"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "int arr[]={1, 2, 3, 4, 5};int x = 4;int y = 0;<br>for(int i = 0; i < 5; i++)y += arr[x - i] * i;<br>System.out.print(y);",
                "type": "input",
                "correctAnswer": "20"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the output?",
                "description": "for (int i = 1, j = 10; i < j; i += i, i++)System.out.print(j - i);",
                "type": "input",
                "correctAnswer": "9985"
            }
        ]
}
